Toni Morrison Papers, 1908-2017: Finding Aid C1491
mss EADs that duplicate ones in Manuscripts
- Working Files, 1955-2018; 68 boxes
  - Book and Project Working Files, 1955-2014; 9 boxes
    - Dreaming Emmett Working Files, 1955-2005; 1 box
      - Dreaming Emmett Photos and Miscellaneous, 1985; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 11)
        Includes photocopied research material and production photographs, contact sheet and rehearsal schedules. For original photographs, see "Skip Dickstein Pix" folder.
      - Dreaming Emmett Pre-performance Discussion Guide, circa 1985; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - Dreaming Emmett Press, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box 124, Folder 13-14)
      - Dreaming Emmett Production Material, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 15)
        Production scripts, blocking notes, rehearsal notes.
      - Dreaming Emmett Publicity, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 16)
      - Dreaming Emmett Requests, 1986-2004; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 17)
      - Dreaming Emmett Research, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 18)
      - Dreaming Emmett Ruth Mott Fund Grant, 1985; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 19)
      - Dreaming Emmett Schedules, 1985; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 20)
      - Dreaming Emmett Skip Dickstein Pix, 1986; 1 folder Black and white contact sheets and photographs, 2 color photographs, photocopies. (Box 124, Folder 21)
        Signed Cynthia Morse.
    - Four Songs Working File, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - God Help the Child Working File, 2014; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Home Working Files, undated; 1 box
      - Home French Translator's Questions, undated; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 24)
      - Home Vintage Reader's Guide, undated; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Honey and Rue Working Files, 1990-1996; 2 folders (Box 124, Folder 26-27)
    - Jazz Working Files, 1991-1997; 2 boxes
      - Jazz 92nd St. Y Reading, 1992; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 28)
        May 19, 1992.
      - Jazz Audio, 1991; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 29)
      - Jazz Book Party, 1992; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 30)
        April 14, 1992.
      - Jazz Chatto & Windus Tour, 1992; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 31)
        January 27-28, 1993.
      - Jazz Correspondence, 1992; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 32)
        Includes drafts of letters from Toni Morrison to Erroll Mcdonald and Amanda Urban.
      - Jazz Denver Reading, 1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 1)
        May 11-12, 1992.
      - Jazz Dutton, 1992-1997; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Jazz Excerpt for Readings, circa 1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Jazz Franklin Library, 1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Jazz Germany/France Tour, 1993; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 5)
        May 7-20, 1993.
      - Jazz Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Jazz Italian Translation, 1993; 2 folders (Box 125, Folder 7-8)
      - Jazz Knopf Canada, 1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - Jazz Knopf USA, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - Jazz London/Paris Tour, 1992; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 11)
        May 30-June 13, 1992.
      - Jazz Michigan/Toronto Tour, 1993; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 12)
        May 1-June 6, 1993.
      - Jazz Picador/Chatto & Windus, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 13)
      - Jazz Spec Script, 1996; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 14)
      - Jazz Sweden/Norway Tour, 1993; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 15)
        October 24-31, 1993.
    - Love Working Files, 2003-2008; 2 boxes
      - Love 92nd St. Y Reading, 2003; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 16)
        December 1, 2003.
      - Love Domestic Tour Schedules, 2003; 3 folders (Box 125, Folder 17-19)
      - Love Essence Excerpt, 2003 October; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 20)
      - Love Foreign Working Files, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 21)
      - Love France/Spain Tour, 2004; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 22)
        May 9-15, 2004.
      - Love Italy Mantova Book Festival, 2004; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 23)
        August 7-12, 2004.
      - Love Knopf, 2003; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 24)
      - Love Reading Princeton University, 2003; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 25)
        November 4, 2003.
      - Love UK Working Files, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 26)
      - Love Vintage, 2004; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 27)
      - Love Vintage Cover Art, 2008; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 16)
    - Margaret Garner Working Files, 1999-2008; 1 box
      - Margaret Garner Charlotte, 2006; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 1)
        April 19, 2006.
      - Margaret Garner Chicago, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 2)
        November 1-9, 2008.
      - Margaret Garner Cincinnati, 2005; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Margaret Garner Detroit, 2005; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 4)
        May 7, 2005.
      - Margaret Garner Miscellaneous, 1999-2004; 2 folders (Box 126, Folder 5-6)
      - Margaret Garner New York City Opera, 2004; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 7)
        May 26, 2004.
      - Margaret Garner New York City Opera, 2007 February; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 8)
        February 20, 2007.
      - Margaret Garner New York City Opera, 2007 April; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 9)
        April 14, 2007.
      - Margaret Garner New York City Opera, 2007 September; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 10)
        September 11-29, 2007.
      - Margaret Garner Philadelphia, 2006; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 11)
        February 10, 2006.
      - Margaret Garner Press, 2005-2006; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - A Mercy Working Files, 2008-2009; 1 box
      - A Mercy 92nd St. Y Reading, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 13)
        December 8, 2008.
      - A Mercy Barnes & Noble Vintage Paperback, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 14)
        August 19, 2009.
      - A Mercy Chatto Editorial, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - A Mercy Editorial, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - A Mercy European Press, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - A Mercy European Tour/Curtis Brown, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 18)
      - A Mercy Foreign Press Requests, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 19)
      - A Mercy France, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 20)
        May 9-17, 2009.
      - A Mercy Holland, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 21)
        May 17-21, 2009.
      - A Mercy Interviews, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 22)
      - A Mercy Italy, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 23)
        May 21-24, 2009.
      - A Mercy Knopf/Random House Canada, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 24)
      - A Mercy National School Boards Association, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 25)
        April 5, 2009.
      - A Mercy O Magazine Pam Houston Interview, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 26)
        April 7, 2009.
      - A Mercy Orange Prize Longlist, 2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 27)
        June 3, 2009.
      - A Mercy Press, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 28)
      - A Mercy Publicity, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 29)
      - A Mercy Random House Audio, 2008; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 30)
        August 8-11, 2008.
      - A Mercy Translation Queries, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - New Orleans Working File, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - Paradise Working Files, 1997-2005 August 5; 3 boxes
      - Paradise Book Party, 1998; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 33)
        January 20, 1998.
      - Paradise California Tour, 1998; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 34)
        July 22-26, 1998.
      - Paradise Germany/Italy Tour, 1999; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 35)
      - Paradise Knopf Canada, 1998; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Paradise Knopf Domestic Tour, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Paradise Knopf Domestic Tour Publicity, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Paradise Miscellaneous, 1997-2000; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Paradise Plume, 1998; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Paradise Publication Denial, 1998 February 20; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Paradise Reader's Guide, 1997; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Paradise Rowohlt German Translators, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - Paradise UK Tour, 1998; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 9)
        May 18-27, 1998.
      - Paradise Miniseries Adaptation, 2005 August 5; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 1)
        Adaptation by Darnell Martin for Harpo Films. Second Draft (4-hour miniseries).
    - Peeny Butter Fudge Working Files, 2009-2012; 1 box
      - Peeny Butter Fudge Simon & Schuster, 2009-2012; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Peeny Butter Fudge Tour, 2009; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 11)
        September 16, 2009.
    - Playing in the Dark Working Files, 1988-2001; 1 box
      - Playing in the Dark Editor Correspondence, 1988-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - Playing in the Dark Grand Street, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - Playing in the Dark Harvard University Press, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - Playing in the Dark Picador, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - Playing in the Dark Press, 1992-2001; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 16)
      - Playing in the Dark Vintage, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Race-ing Justice Working Files, 1991-2003; 2 boxes
      - Race-ing Justice Homi Bhaba, 1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 18)
      - Race-ing Justice Claudia Brodsky Lacour, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 19)
      - Race-ing Justice Margaret Burnham, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 20)
      - Race-ing Justice Kimberle Crenshaw, 1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 21)
      - Race-ing Justice Paula Giddings, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 22)
      - Race-ing Justice Leon Higginbotham, Jr., 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 23)
      - Race-ing Justice Wahneema Lubiano, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 24)
      - Race-ing Justice Manning Marable, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 25)
      - Race-ing Justice Nellie McKay, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 26)
      - Race-ing Justice Nell Painter, undated; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 27)
      - Race-ing Justice Gayle Pemberton, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 28)
      - Race-ing Justice Andrew Ross, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 29)
      - Race-ing Justice Christine Stansell, undated; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 30)
      - Race-ing Justice Carol Swain, 1991; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 31)
      - Race-ing Justice Michael Thelwell, undated; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 32)
      - Race-ing Justice Kendall Thomas, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 33)
      - Race-ing Justice Cornel West, undated; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Race-ing Justice Patricia Williams, 1991; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Race-ing Justice Chatto & Windus, 1992; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Race-ing Justice Contributors, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Race-ing Justice Miscellaneous, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Race-ing Justice Pantheon, 1991-2003; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Race-ing Justice Philadelphia Forum, 1992; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Race-ing Justice Publicity, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Race-ing Justice Reviews, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - "Recitatif" Working File, 1981-1990; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Remember: The Journey to School Integration Working File, 2003-2005; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Song of Solomon Working Files, 1977-1996; 1 box
      - Song of Solomon Book of the Month Club, 1977; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 12)
      - Song of Solomon Correspondence re: Adaptation, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - Song of Solomon Knopf Publicity, 1977; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 14)
      - Song of Solomon Plume/Random House, 1996; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 15)
      - Song of Solomon Reynolds Price Introduction, 1995; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Sula Working Files, 1984-2001; 2 boxes
      - Sula Catalan Translation, 1995; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 17)
      - Sula Film, 1984-1994; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 18)
      - Sula Picador Cover Art, undated; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 17)
      - Sula Screenplay, 2001; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Sweet Talk Working File, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Tar Baby Working Files, 1983-1995; 1 box
      - Tar Baby Film Inquiries, 1986-1995; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 21)
      - Tar Baby French Translation, 1986; 2 folders (Box 128, Folder 22-23)
      - Tar Baby Screenplay, 1983; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 24)
      - Tar Baby Screenplay, 1991; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 25)
      - Tar Baby Screenplay, 1994; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 26)
      - Tar Baby Screenplay, 1995 February 19; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Who's Got Game Working Files, 2002-2007; 1 box
      - Who's Got Game Pascal Lemaître, 2002-2004; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 28)
      - Who's Got Game Scribner/Simon & Schuster, 2002-2007; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 29)
  - Office Working Files I, 1970-1988; 5 boxes
    Consists of alphabetical subject files.
    The original order of these files was maintained.
    - Academic Correspondence, 1978-1984; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - American Writers Congress, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - "Are You Interested?", 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Author Correspondence, 1973-1985; 2 folders (Box 129, Folder 4-5)
    - Authors Guild, 1977; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Awards, 1978-1982; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Bibliography, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Biography/Resume, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Black Picture Show - Bill Gunn, undated; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Blurb Requests, 1973-1986; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Book Ads, undated; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Book Covers, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - China, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Commitments, 1979-1985; 6 folders (Box 129, Folder 15-20)
    - Congratulations, 1974-1982; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1985; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Declines, 1977-1981 August; 6 folders (Box 129, Folder 23-28)
    - Declines, 1981 September-1985; 11 folders (Box 130, Folder 1-11)
    - Fan Mail, 1970-1985; 4 folders (Box 130, Folder 12-15)
    - Faulkner Conference, 1985; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - FBI File on Toni Morrison, 1972; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Guardian, 1973; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Grandview Library, 1986; 2 folders (Box 130, Folder 19-20)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1983; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Indexing, 1985; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Information from T., 1985; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Interviews, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Interviews, 1982-1986; 2 folders (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
    - Interviews (Press), 1977-1986; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Judgment Ridge, undated; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Legal, 1978-1985; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Libraries (requests for TM's manuscripts), 1979-1988; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - List of Photos of Toni Morrison, undated; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - McKeever, Herman, Poetry, 1974; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Memorabilia, 1979-1987; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1984; 2 folders (Box 131, Folder 10-11)
    - MLA, 1984; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - NEA Correspondence, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - NEA Five-Year Plan, 1985; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - New York Public Library, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Paris: Ampart Tour, 1985 March-August; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Paris: Memorabilia, 1985 May; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Paris: Droits de l'Homme, 1985 May 29; 2 folders (Box 131, Folder 18-19)
    - PEN, 1983-1986; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - People's World, 1973; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Plans and Projects (Other People's), 1977-1984; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Preservation, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Professional Organizations, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Projects: Theater, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Chatto, 1978-1985; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Doubleday, 1978-1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Foreign, 1978-1985; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Holt, 1970-1983; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Publishers Correspondence: ICM, 1977-1985; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Knopf, 1977-1983; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1972-1985; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Publishers Correspondence: Random House, 1971-1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Readings, 1978-1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Recommendations (For Other People), 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 1)
      This material is closed until 2085, or until the death of the subject of letter.
    - Resources, 1984-1986; 3 folders (Box 132, Folder 10-12)
    - The Roaring Twenties, 1972; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Speeches I, 1979-1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Speeches II, 1981; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Speeches III, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Speeches IV, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Speeches V, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - SUNY Albany, 1983-1986; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - SUNY Purchase, 1971; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - Teaching - Bard, 1979; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - Teaching - Rutgers, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Travel Info, 1984; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - United States Information Agency (USIA), 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Video, 1983; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 25)
    - Writers and Artists Club (WAC), 1973; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 26)
    - Writers Guild of America, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - Office Working Files II, 1971-2012; 26 boxes
    Consists of files documenting accepted and declined activities and events followed by alphabetical subject files.
    - Accepted Awards, 1987-1990; 1 box
      - Accepted Awards, 1987; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 1)
        Ms. Magazine Woman of the Year Award (12/17/87), Anson Phelps Stoke Fundraising Benefit (11/19/87), National Book Award (11/9/87), Washington College Literary Award (3/26-28/87), College of St. Rose "Conversations" and Honorary Degree (3/10/87).
      - Accepted Awards, 1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Accepted Awards, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Accepted Commitments, 1984-1989; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Accepted Conferences, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Accepted Interviews, 1985-1995; 1 box
      - Accepted Interviews, 1985-1990; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 6)
        Aesthetics Research Archive; New Directions; Il Giornale/Mario Materassi (5/88); Presence Africaine (1990); Yale Vernacular (1990); Interview Correspondence (1985); Accepted Interviews (1986); General Interview Requests (1986-1988).
      - Accepted Interviews, 1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Belles Lettres, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Callaloo on L. Forrest, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - Paris Review, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - Princeton Weekly Bulletin, 1993; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - Radiotelevisione della Svizzera italiana, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - Time Magazine, 1993; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 13)
      - Trans World International, 1993; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 14)
      - UK Channel 4/Lisa Appignamesi, 1991; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Accepted Lectures, 1985-1990; 1 box
      - Accepted Lectures, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 16)
        SUNY Purchase (April-May 1988), Bowdoin College (September 1987), Scripps College (10/22-23/87), City Arts & Lectures/Friends of the San Francisco Public Library (10/8/87), Regents Lecture UC Berkeley (October-November 1987), UC Santa Barbara.
      - Accepted Lectures, 1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 17)
      - Accepted Lectures, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 18)
      - Tanner Lecture, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Accepted Miscellaneous, 1985-1994; 1 box
      - Accepted Miscellaneous, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 20)
      - Accepted Miscellaneous, 1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 21)
      - Accepted Miscellaneous, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 22)
      - Accepted Miscellaneous, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 23)
    - Accepted Readings, 1986-1990; 1 box
      - Accepted Readings, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 24)
      - Accepted Readings, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 25)
      - Accepted Readings, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 26)
    - Accepted SUNY Albany, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 27)
    - Declines, 1985 December-1992; 2 boxes
      - Declines, 1985 December-1986 July; 2 folders (Box 133, Folder 28-29)
      - Declines, 1986 August-1987 March; 2 folders (Box 133, Folder 30-31)
      - Declines, 1987 April-September; 2 folders (Box 133, Folder 32-33)
      - Declines, 1987 October-December; 2 folders (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
      - Declines, 1988; 3 folders (Box 134, Folder 3-5)
      - Declines, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 134, Folder 6-7)
        Declined commencement, awards, other, guest/keynote speaker, readings, lectures.
      - Declines, 1989; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Declines, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 134, Folder 9-10)
        Declined awards, lectures, conferences, commencement, college and school appearances, other, guest/keynote speaker, interviews.
      - Declines, 1991-1992; 3 folders (Box 134, Folder 11-13)
        Declined awards, college, commencements, conferences, keynote speaker, lecture, other, symposium/panels, readings, read ms, schools, in residence.
    - Declined Albany, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Declined Awards, 1992-2004; 1 box
      - Declined Awards, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Declined Awards, 1995-2000; 2 folders (Box 135, Folder 2-3)
      - Declined Awards, 2000-2004; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Declined College & High School Appearances, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Declined Conferences and Commencements, 1992-2005; 1 box
      - Declined Conferences and Commencements, 1992-1996; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Declined Conferences and Commencements, 1994-2000; 2 folders (Box 135, Folder 7-8)
      - Declined Conferences, 2000-2005; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Declined Festivals, 1993-2007; 1 box
      - Declined Festivals, 1993-1998; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Declined Festivals, 1998-2005; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Declined Festivals, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Declined Fundraisers, 1993-2007; 2 boxes
      - Declined Fundraisers, 1993-1997; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - Declined Fundraisers, 1994-2000; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 14)
      - Declined Fundraisers, 1997 October-1998 December; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Declined Fundraisers, 2001-2003; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 2-3)
      - Declined Fundraisers, 2002-2005; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Declined Fundraisers, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Declined Guest/Keynote Speaker, 1993-2007; 2 boxes
      - Declined Guest/Keynote Speaker, 1993; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Declined Guest/Keynote Speaker, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Declined Guest/Keynote Speaker, 1994; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Declined Guest/Keynote Speaker, 1996-1998; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 9-10)